各位我的支持者们 因你们我才得到了大众选票的多数票
And to the American people who supported me
我向你们保证
with a majority of the popular vote,
这项绝佳的清洁能源合资企业...
I promise you, this amazing clean energy joint venture with...
温蒂和我在找代孕
You know, Wendy and I have been meeting with surrogates.
她兴冲冲地要把我的
She is so excited about
精子塞给另一个女人 太别扭了
my sperm being in another woman. It's weird.
乘着经济改革的东风
For the winds of economic change...
这是振奋人心的事
they are a blowing.
谢谢 非常感谢
Thank you. Thank you very much.
- 总统女士 - 非常感谢
- Madam President. - Thank you very much.
为什么我的头发被吹得打圈
Why is my hair all spinning around
这些玩意却和你一样 闲着不动?
and these things, like you, are doing nothin'?
很显然风速太快的时候
Apparently they shut the
他们就关掉了风力涡轮
turbines off if the wind speeds are too high.
还来得及把它们改成石油井架吗?
Is it too late to turn them into oil derricks?
女士 坏消息
Ma'am, I just got some really sad news.
- 你妈住院了 - 什么?
- Your mother's in the hospital. - What?
- 好像是中风 - 又来?
- It looks like a stroke. - Again?
我们可以取消和工程师的见面会
We can eighty-six the meet-and-greet with the engineers.
- 应该没大问题 - 为什么?
- That's no problem. - Why?
因为你得赶到母亲的床头啊
Because you need to rush to your mother's bedside.
- 是啊 - 好吧 那我...
- Yeah. - All right. Okay. I'm...
希望外婆没事
I hope Mee-Maw's okay.
死神都敲了她五次门了
She's been at death's door like five times,
- 但她总能恢复元气 - 确实如此
- but she always bounces back to life. - It's true.
她就和那个谁一样
She's like that guy... that guy...
- 拉撒路[圣经中被耶稣复活] - 拉斯普金[俄国僧人被暗杀五次才死亡]
- Lazarus. - Rasputin.
她上次来白宫的时候看起来特别亲切
She seemed sweet when she visited the White House.
是吗? 我和你们说
Really? Let me tell you something.
我第一次竞选州参议员失败后
After I lost my first election for state senate,
妈妈告诉我"这不是你的错
Mother says to me, "Well, it's not your fault.
错的是你露出牙齿的笑容"
It's just your toothy smile."
我的天 我爱死你的笑容啦
Oh, my God. I love your smile.
这不是重点
That's not the point.
你不露牙的话更奇怪
Looks weirder if you don't show your teeth.
我只是不敢相信
I just cannot believe that this has happened
在有这么多事情的时候她病了
in the middle of all of this.
我懂的 跟你说 我妈妈得卵巢癌的时候...
I know. I know. I'll tell you, when my mom got ovarian cancer...
对了 打给肯特
Oh, call Kent.
选票听证会
内华达州最高法院
这正是为什么我们要制止
And that is why we have to stop
选举人票选过程中这种草率的干预
this reckless meddling in the electoral process.
坚守法律底线
Stick to the legal deadline
保证选票的公正性
and certify the count as it stands.
谢谢您 法官大人
Thank you, Your Honors.
庭上 请允许我
May it please the court,
我们可以站在法庭上
there are many things that we could all stand here
无休止地就很多事进行辩论
and debate for hours on end.
天是蓝的吗? 水是湿的吗?
Is the sky blue? Is water wet?
但是拘泥于仲裁期限
But isn't it far worse to adhere to an arbitrary deadline
不是比统计所有有效票要糟得多吗?
rather than counting every valid vote?
上帝啊 选举人票选抗议?
Jesus, an electoral protest?
等一下 那是奥布莱恩那边的猎头 选票重计时见过
Wait a second, that's the O'Brien nimrod from the recount table.
假抗议 典型的奥布莱恩式行为
A fake protest. That is classic O'Brien.
真他妈卑鄙
It's such a scumbag move.
这无休无尽的选票重计得结束了
this endless recount's got to go.
是啊 我要去弄点零钱
Yep, I'll raid petty cash.
贞女医院
马里兰州银春区
夫人 您得看下奥布莱恩这个蠢货的推文
Ma'am, you have to see this dumb O'Brien tweet.
"又是浪费纳税人钱财的一天
"Another day wasting taxpayer dollars.
梅耶风车项目费钱又没用”
Meyer plus windmills cost money, do nothing."
这得怪你 你说呢?
Well, that's on you, isn't it?
风车不转今天你试试脑子转起来好吗?
See if you can spin something right today, okay?
- 天哪 - 夫人 艾米打电话来了
- God. - Ma'am, Amy's calling.
艾米 怎么了?
Ame, hi. What's going on?
夫人 我感到非常非常抱歉
Ma'am, I'm so, so sorry.
- 怎么? 发生了什么? - 什么?
- What? What happened? - What?
你妈妈 我在赫芬顿邮报上看到她住院了
Your mother. I read on HuffPo that she was in the hospital.
艾米 我还以为你说的是选票重计呢
Amy, I thought you were talking about the recount.
再也不要像这样吓我了
Don't ever, ever scare me like that again.
- 不好意思 - 不惜一切代价
- I'm sorry. - Just do whatever it takes
把选票算进去懂了吗?
to get these ballots counted, okay?
我妈妈会没事的 我得挂了
My mother's gonna be fine. I gotta go.
- 我的上帝啊 我们刚... - 好的
- God, we just... - Okay.
每个人都在呢
Oh, wow. Everyone's here.
这是你暂时的移动办公室
This is your temporary mobile oval.
不好意思 请问这有小水壶或者蒸汽熨斗吗?
I'm sorry, is there a kettle or clothing steamer in here?
- 没有 - 好吧 今天会是难熬的一天
- No. - Okay, this is gonna be quite the day.
我妈妈在哪儿?
So where's my mother?
- 她在大厅右手边 - 好的
- She's down the hall to the right. - Okay.
- 安德鲁也来了 - 什么?
- And Andrew's here. - What?
- 真的假的? - 是凯瑟琳要求的
- What? - At Catherine's request.
但我保证了他连坐的地方都没有
But I made sure he had nowhere to sit.
苏 你真善良
You are good people, Sue.
安德鲁
Andrew.
好啊 你来的挺快
Wow, hi. You got here quick.
凯瑟琳打电话给我的 你在外面?
Catherine called me. You were away?
是啊 为国家服务
Yeah, serving the country.
- 对你妈妈的事感到很抱歉 - 谢谢
- I'm sorry about your mother. - Thank you.
这是莫妮卡
Oh, this is Monica.
很高兴见到你 总统女士
A pleasure to meet you, Madam President.
我的心与你同在
My thoughts are so with you right now.
非常感谢
Thank you so much.
- 你带了伴儿来 - 我不认识她
- You brought a date. - I don't know her.
莫妮卡和我在一起呢  她是我生命的一部分
Monica and I are seeing one another. She's part of my life.
她写家政方面的书籍
She writes books on homemaking.
- 还写娱乐方面的博客 - 我还真知道她
- Blogs about entertaining. - I do know her.
她还做一些地方晨间节目
She does some of the local morning shows.
- 节假日也会上WBAL台[NBC旗下] - 我的天哪
- WBAL has her on during the holidays. - Oh, my God.
好啦 亲爱的
Okay, sweetie, the president
总统现在一定不想听我的个人简历
does not want to hear my resume right now.
她很聪明啊 你学学
She's a smart one. You can maybe pick up something from her.
- 谢谢 - 不用谢
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
我老婆特别爱你的香料蛋酒
I just want to say my wife is obsessed with your spiced eggnog.
- 我们一整年都在喝那个 - 做冰淇淋也特好吃
- We drink it year-round. - It makes a really yummy ice cream.
- 真的嘛 - 是啊
- Shut up. - Yeah.
- 亲爱的 - 妈妈好
- Hi, sweetie. - Hi, Mom.
凯瑟琳 这是...
Oh, Catherine, this is...
- 凯瑟琳 - 很感谢您能来
- Hey, Cat. - Thank you so much for coming.
你们俩认识?
You two know each other?
我们一起出去过几次
We've all been hanging out a bunch.
莫莫还给了我这件毛衣
Yeah, Monnie gave me this sweater.
不 我绝对没给过你那毛衣
No, I definitely didn't give you that sweater.
- 还是那种颜色 - 不 我没有
- Not that color. - No, I didn't.
不好意思 她说的是我
I'm sorry, I think she's talking about me.
她叫我"莫莫" 听上去像"妈妈"
She calls me "Monnie." Sounds like "Mommy."
好吧
Mm-hmm. Well, okay.
- 我真受不了这音乐了 - 就是啊
- I can't take this music, okay? - Yeah, please.
这竞选都结束了
I mean, the campaign's over. I
我不用继续假装喜欢乡村音乐了
don't have to pretend to like country music anymore.
这蒂姆·麦格罗唱的 是外婆最喜欢的歌
This is Tim McGraw. It's Mee-Maw's favorite song.
啥? 不 她最喜欢的
What? No. Mee-Maw's favorite song
只要是内曼·马库斯奢侈品专卖店背景音乐就成
is whatever is playing in the background at Neiman Marcus.
能不能麻利地关了?
Please turn it off, okay?
妈 你应该和她打声招呼
Mom, you should say hi to her.
亲爱哒 如果我想和一个没意识的人说话
Honey, if I wanted to talk to an unconscious person,
我就去上查理·罗斯的节目了[美国主播 脱口秀主持人]
I'd book myself on Charlie Rose.
她指甲怎么了?
What happened to her nails?
像她用手挖过土豆一样
Looks like she's been diggin' for potatoes or something.
你现在怎么竟然还在操心她的指甲?
Why are you even worried about her hands right now?
这压根不重要
That is so not important.
- 凯瑟琳 奶奶最爱她指甲了 - 对呀
- Catherine, Mother loves her hands. - Yeah.
她给我洗澡的时候都戴着洗碗的手套
She always wore dishwashing gloves when she gave me my bath.
这好像是我不洗碗的原因
Which is why I don't do dishes.
我刚意识到
I just now realized that.
你好 总统女士
Hello, Madam President.
我是米尔普里医生
I'm Dr. Mirpuri.
- 米尔...  - 米尔普里
- Dr. Mir - Mirpuri.
"米尔 普里." 她现在情况如何?
"Mir-piri." Okay. How is she doing?
情况相当不妙
I'm afraid it's quite dire.
大脑功能全部中断
All brain function has ceased.
所以是她醒不过来的意思?
So she's not gonna bounce back?
她恐怕得靠维持机维持生命了
I'm afraid she'll need to stay on life support
直至大限之日
until she expires.
你还想帮她修修指甲吗?
Did you still want to do her nails?
- 当然 - 好嘞
- Oh, yes, I do. - Okay.
医院餐厅 一楼
不 我们不用那女人
No, we're not hiring that woman.
她嘴上只是感冒疮啊 亲爱的
It was just a cold sore, honey.
我可不想花四万刀换个有疱疹的宝宝[一般为性病]
I don't want to pay 40 grand for a herpes baby.
- 你好你是黛博拉莉? - 对 你好
- Oh, hey, Debralee? - Yes, hi.
迈克 对 很高兴认识你
Mike, yes. Nice to meet you.
- 温蒂 - 黛博拉莉 你好 温蒂 也很高兴认识你
- Wendy. - Debralee. Hi, Wendy. So nice to meet you.
- 来点什么吗? - 不用 谢谢
- You want anything? - I'm good. Thank you, though.
来这路上我喝了点康普茶
I just had a kombucha on my way over.
- 那我就直奔话题了 - 那太棒了
- Okay, so I'll just dive on in... - That'd be great.
给你们交代一下我的背景
and give you guys a little background on me.
你们已经知道成功代孕了三个宝宝
You already know I've carried three babies to term.
我吃用全部是有机的 每天锻炼
Keep everything organic. I exercise every day.
我从不吸烟喝酒
I don't drink or smoke and I never have.
那太棒了
That's amazing.
你正是我们要找的那个人
I mean, that's exactly what we're looking for.
赞美耶稣
Praise Jesus.
你们都是基督徒吗?
Are y'all Christians?
对 对
Yes. Mm-hmm, yes.
很多人都觉得我是犹太人 但 不
I mean, a lot of people think that I'm Jewish, but that-- no.
你们都去哪些教堂?
What church y'all go to?
- 圣女... - 圣洁的子宫...
- Our Lady... - Of the Holy Womb...
- ...圣洁的子宫 - ...耶稣的子宫
- ...of the Holy Womb. - ...Womb of Jesus.
就一个小教会 但是挺激进的
It's a small congregation, but it's fierce.
很神圣
It's holy.
艾米丽正在修她的指甲
Okay, Emily's working on her nails now.
- 好 - 打扰一下 总统女士
- Good. - Excuse me, Madam President.
您母亲没有决定最后要不要放弃抢救
Your mother was a bit vague on the DNR.
- 好 - 所以要您来决定了
- Okay. - So it will come down to you.
- 让我们期盼奇迹吧 - 别
- Praying for a miracle. - Please don't.
好
Okay.
Um, okay.
迈克普里医生
Well, Dr. McCurry
- 米尔普里 - 对 就这意思
- Mirpuri. - Yes, that's what I said.
具体是什么意思呢 要把她维持生命的插头拔了?
So what does that entail, you know, the pulling of the plug?
其实没有插头
There's not really a plug.
只要去除呼吸机管
What we're talking about requires removing the ventilator tube.
然后她的各种器官就会开始衰竭
And then as her organs begin to fail
天 我得坐下缓缓
Okay, I'm gonna have to sit down for just a minute,
如果可以的话
if that's all right.
我们会持续观察她的生命迹象
We would be tracking her vitals
这没事 凯瑟琳 别担心
It's okay, Catherine. It's okay.
啊 这就有点大声了 亲
Oh, wow, that is loud, honey.
那也忒大声了
That's loud.
这"斯蒂芬·霍金"也不舒服了 我还是...
Oh, "Stephen Hawking" Here is indisposed, so I'll just...
- 马乔里 你能帮我处理好这档子破事吗? - 好的 女士
- Marjorie, can you help me with this? - Yes, ma'am.
我仅想向您保证 总统女士
I just want to assure you, Madam President,
我们将竭尽所能以保证...
we would do everything in our power to ensure
等等 这突然有急事 肯特!
Yeah, just a sec. Something's pressing here. Kent!
- 不好意思 不是有意打扰 - 不不不
- I'm sorry, didn't mean to intrude. - No, no, no.
我故意选择了一条别人听不见的地方
I chose a parabolic path deliberately out of earshot.
没事
It's fine.
怎么了?
What's up?
我就是想
I just needed to get a
从外面那个印度死神那里缓缓
break from the Hindu Grim Reaper out there.
我不知道这能不能提供些安慰
I don't know if this provides any solace,
但自从您母亲病危的消息传出
but ever since your mother's health setback was announced,
民众一直表现出对您的支持...
there has been an outpouring of support...
...也提升了您的受欢迎度
...that has driven up your favorables.
我是在说要不要拔出她的插头
I'm talking about pulling the plug on my mother here.
就0.5%的民调怎么能
How is half a percentage point in the polls
让糟糕的情况好转一点?
supposed to sweeten that shit biscuit?
- 上升的可是双位数 - 讲真?
- More like double digits. - Really?
但我就好奇想问问啊
But just out of curiosity,
如果我要 你懂
if I were to, you know...
民调上升会停止吗?
uh, would that end?
可能会出现一个短暂的
There is a possibility of a shorter-lived,
更大幅度的上涨
but numerically greater outpouring
可以叫"死亡跳跃"
if you will, a "Death bump."
- 讲真? -真
- Really? - Really.
真是疯狂而沉重啊
Well, that is some wild and heavy stuff.
确实
Indeed.
我得好好检索我的灵魂了
Yeah. I got some real soul-searching to do.
我已经在华盛顿待了很长时间了
Now, I have been in Washington a long time
我以为我什么都见过了
and I thought I had seen everything,
但是奥布莱恩参议员表现出来的泠漠
but the insensitivity shown by Senator O'Brien
很明显说明
clearly demonstrates that this
这个男人并不拥有判断力与尊严...
man does not possess the judgment and dignity...
真理啊
True statesman right there.
好的吧 我现在需要一个安静的地方来思考
Okay, so now what I need is a quiet place to think
这地方不能有迈克那张蠢脸
that doesn't have Mike's stupid face in it.
我转身 女士
I can turn around, ma'am.
四楼有个小教堂
There's a chapel on the fourth floor.
可以订给您使用
We can make sure it's cleared out for you.
好 棒
Okay, yeah.
- 女士? - 怎么?
- Ma'am? - What?
我们所爱的永不逝去
Those we have loved cannot be lost
因为他们已经与我们融为一体
because they are always a part of us.
谢谢啊 本 顺带感谢写那句话的人
Thank you, Ben, and whoever wrote those words.
- 看我发现了什么 - 晚了
- Look what I found. - Too late.
- 当然 - 我记得这句话
- Of course. - I recognize those words.
我的猫去世时
They were in the card your
你妻子送我的卡片上有
wife sent me when my cat Fibonacci passed.
很安慰
I found them soothing.
这没完的重新计票必须结束
This endless recount's got to go.
- 好口号啊 - 朗朗上口
- God, that's a great chant. - Just catchy.
天呐 把证件收起来
Jesus, lose the fucking badge, man.
天呐 让我看看成品
Jesus Christ. All right, show me the art.
我们有"选举"头头"票"
We got "Count Totes the Votes."
这是什么?什么是"头头"?
What is that? What's "Totes"?
"头头" 就像是 统计所有的票
Totes, like all. Count all the votes.
你们只有一件工作 就是把人群聚起来
You guys have one job to do, that is to rally the crowd
带着支持总统的标语
with your pro-POTUS signs
让你们不上镜的脸上电视
and get your camera-unfriendly faces on TV.
- 没错 - 你不能让乔纳·瑞安就这样出现在电视上
- Yes. - You can't put a Jonah Ryan on TV like that.
18到34岁的女性都会被严重干扰的
18 to 34-year-old women are gonna be distracted by that.
18到34岁的女性如果看到你出现在电视里
The only thing that women 18-34 are gonna do
唯一会做的就是申请一份限制令
when they see you on camera is file a restraining order.
所以制造点动静吧 笨蛋们
So make some fuckin' noise, dummies.
你他妈的笑什么?
What the fuck are you smiling at?
我只是很高兴在这里
I'm just happy to be here.
不可置信
Unbelievable.
我们想要什么? 计票
What do we want? To get the votes counted.
什么时候要? 希望在截止之前
When do we want it? Hopefully before the deadline.
斯隆家庭追悼厅
- 你祈祷吗? - 经常
- Do you pray? - A lot.
你祈祷些什么?
What do you pray for?
你懂的...
You, you know...
你想不想试试?
Do you want - you maybe want to try it?
行啊
Sure.
管他的呢? 我们已经在这了 对吧?
You know, what the hell? We're here, right?
- 对呀 - 好
- Okay, all right. - Yeah.
好
Okay.
上帝 我...
God, I...
我... 我就是... 我很...
I... I just... I'm...
"主啊 是我 赛琳娜"
"O Lord God, it's me, Selina."
主啊 是我  赛琳娜...
O Lord God. It's me, Selina...
请授予我智慧和力量
Grant me wisdom and strength.
让我们知道您的存在... 我自己来
Give us Your comforting presence... I've got it now.
- 我可以来 - 好的
- I've got it. - Okay, yep.
主啊 请缓解我的母亲的痛苦与折磨
Lord God, please ease my mother's pain and suffering.
是的 上帝 是的 上帝
Yes, Lord. Yes, Lord.
缓解她的消逝 缓解所有
Ease her passing. Ease it all.
- 是的 - 缓解降低至...
- Yes. - Ease it down the
- 嗯 - 至...
- Mmm. - the...
主啊 让她的女儿 谦虚的仆人
Lord, let her daughter, Thy humble servant,
成为美国第一个女总统吧
be the first woman elected President of the United States.
拜托了主 一切都太沉重了
Please, this is so much to bear.
是真的 主 真的
Oh, it is, Lord. It is.
- 听见我的祷告 - 听听她的祷告
- Hear my prayer. - Hear her prayer.
- 让我升上去 - 让她升上去 主
- Lift me up. - Lift her up, Lord.
不 我是说真的把我抬起来
No, I mean actually lift
我的高跟鞋卡在这里了
me up 'cause my heel is stuck in this thing.
好的
Yeah, I got it.
好 告诉你一声
Um, okay, just so you know,
等那个呼吸机弄走了之后
after the ventilator is removed,
- 可能会引起一些咳嗽 - 哦
- there might be some coughing. - Oh.
就是一种反射反应 并不表示她醒了
It's reflexive. It's not a sign that she's aware
- 或是很痛苦之类的 - 好的
- or suffering in any way. - Okay.
好的 我给你一些时间告别
Okay, why don't I give you a moment to say goodbye?
你是指现在? 什么
Oh, you mean now? What
这就好多了
Well, that's much better.
妈妈...
Well, Mother...
我只想让你...
I just want you to...
我们所爱的永不逝去
those you loved cannot be lost
因为他们已经与我们融为一体
because they are always a part of you.
所以...
So...
好的
Okay.
- 女士? - 怎么了?
- Ma'am? - Yeah?
抱歉 我的事情可以等一会
Sorry, it can wait till later.
- 不用 进来吧 - 你确定?
- No, no, come in. - You sure?
对 请进
Yeah, come in.
米尔... 医生? 你能... 对
Yeah, Doctor Mir... ? Can... yeah.
好的 妮可 你可以开始了
Okay, Nicole, you can go ahead and begin.
女士 我们在这不合适吧
Ma'am, I don't really think we should be here for this.
你们留下 留下
No, no, you've got to stay. You're gonna stay.
好的 她要移开呼吸机了
Okay, she's just gonna remove the ventilator.
好的
Okay.
什么...?
What...?
所以按你的经验讲
So in your experience,
这种事情一般要多久?
how long does this sort of thing carry on?
- 通常几分钟 - 好的
- Usually minutes. - Okay.
- 我见过几小时的 - 嗯?
- I have seen hours. - Huh?
几天的就很少见了
Days are very rare.
好吧 这可不行
Oh, well, that's not gonna work
因为我的行程安排和生活
because for me with my schedule and life.
天哪
Jesus Christ.
关了
Turn that off.
好的 别...
Okay, no...
她已经去了 总统女士
Um, she's gone, Madam President.
- 嗯 好的 - 节哀
- Yeah, okay. - My condolences.
- 我能独处一会吗? - 当然了
- Can I just have a moment? - Yes, of course. Absolutely.
你怎么不看看你的手机呢?
Well, why don't you check your phones?
听起来就像你偷了好多振动棒一样
Sounds like you shoplifted a bunch of vibrators.
内华达州最高法庭
The Nevada State Supreme Court
签署了一个暂时的认证
issued a temporary stay of certification.
重计还会继续
The count will continue.
- 我的祷告奏效了 对吧? - 可能
- Oh, my prayer worked, right? - Maybe.
你想要天助 天助真的来了
Wow, you wanted help from above, here it is.
太棒啦
Yeah. It's fantastic.
妈? 发生什么了? 大家都在欢呼什么?
Mom? What's going on? What's everyone cheering about?
- 是外婆好起来了吗? - 凯瑟琳
- Is Mee-Maw better? - Catherine.
我以为你一直在这呢
I thought you were here.
没有 我出去喝点咖啡
No, I went to get coffee.
我还问你要不要
I asked if you wanted anything.
没 我没听见啊
No, I didn't hear you say that.
她去世了?
She's gone?
我不在的时候你拔了插头?
You pulled the plug without me?
那不是个插头 是个呼吸机管...
It wasn't a plug. It was a ventilator tube that they just...
亲爱的
Oh, darling.
亲爱的 不 不
Oh, honey, no, no, no, no.
外婆不会知道你不在这的 亲爱的
Mee-Maw didn't know you weren't here, honey.
她当时都脑死亡了
She's brain dead.
宝宝 她脑死亡了
Baby doll, she was brain dead.
我们有一些好消息
We got good news
关于内华达
about Nevada.
等一下 什么?
Wait, what?
内华达有好消息
We got good news from Nevada.
妈?
Mom?
- 我就先出去了 - 好的
- I'm gonna step outside. - Okay.
马里兰 小乐山
妈妈从来不让我用好的钢琴
Mother would never let me use the good piano.
我一直得在那个屎一样的小房间里上课
I always had to take my lessons on the shitty upright in the den.
你知道吗?
Oh, you know what?
我可以把这故事放悼词里
That would be a good story for the eulogy.
妈咪 你为什么
Mom, why would you want
要把外婆描绘的这么负面?
to paint Mee-Maw in such a negative light?
凯瑟琳 狗日的托马斯·金凯德[天才画家 以色调鲜明著称]
Oh, Catherine, Thomas fucking Kinkade
都没法正面描绘你外婆
couldn't paint Mee-Maw in a positive light.
我的天呐
Oh, my God.
你都没见过外公
You never knew Daddy.
他超贴心的 他去世你外婆怪我
He was so sweet. Mee-Maw blamed me for his death.
什么?
What?
只是你自己这么想吧
I think that's probably your interpretation of it.
凯瑟琳 你根本无法想象
Oh, Catherine, you have no idea
当一个病态的自恋狂
what it was like to be the only daughter
唯一的女儿要忍受些什么
of a pathological narcissist.
这个女人只会挑我的错 或者无视我
I mean, all this woman did was criticize me or ignore me.
我要去睡了
I'm gonna go to bed.
去吧 晚安
Okay, night.
睡觉别用那些枕头
The pillows are not for sleeping.
女士 您母亲的律师乔治·亨辛格到了
Ma'am, your mother's attorney George Huntzinger is here.
好的 乔治叔叔
Okay. Uncle George.
- 赛琳娜 - 喔!
- Selina. - Oh!
或者我该说总统女士?
Or should I say Madam President?
我的天呐
Oh, my goodness.
见到你真是太高兴了
I'm so happy to see you.
你知道么? 妈妈的律师里面
You know what? You were always my favorite
我最喜欢你了
of all of Mother's lawyers.
- 你太客气了 - 我认真的
- You're too kind. - No, it's true.
我应该把妈妈避暑别墅的钥匙
So we need to get you the keys
给你带给评估人对吧
to Mother's summer house for the appraisers.
就在这边吧? 好的
Right over here? Yeah.
她可是个好人啊
She was the most darling woman.
是啊 某种意义上还真是的
Yes, she certainly was in a sense, yeah.
- 给您钥匙 先生 - 这就行了
- Here's the key, sir. - There we go.
女士 我们必须尽快继续计划葬礼了
Ma'am, we really need to return to funeral planning.
- 好的 - 外面人太多了
- Yes. - So many people outside.
恐怕我得开车压过他们才能进来了
I feared I might have to start driving over them to get in here.
是么? 是抗议者么?
Really? Protesters?
这个国家连一点礼仪都没有了
This country's just lost its sense of decency.
- 都是些禽兽 - 不不 天呐 不是的
- Well, they're animals. - No, no. Heavens, no.
- 他们都是祈福的人 - 真的么?
- They're well-wishers. - Really?
是的
Yeah.
人们竟然在替我祈福?
People are wishing me well?
当然啦 你在守孝啊
Well, of course they are. You're in mourning.
没错 对
Oh, right. Yeah.
太感谢你了 真是太客气了
Thank you so much. You're too kind.
我十分感激
I appreciate it.
我的神啊 感觉我是个新娘一样
Oh, my goodness. I feel like a bride.
悲伤的新娘 当然了 今天太不幸了
A sad bride because, of course, this is a day of grief.
她脑袋不清醒已经有一阵了
Her brain was quite damaged for quite a long time.
我也爱你
I love you.
这有太多友好且多样的面孔了
There are so many friendly and diverse faces here.
我真希望母亲还活着
And I wish that Mother were alive
可以亲眼看到此情此景
to see this on her property.
内华达选举委员会
奥布莱恩
O'Brien.
布鲁克海默小姐 票数重计的怎么样了?
Ms. Brookheimer, how goes the count?
简直好极了
Oh, it's great if you want
如果你希望一个傲慢的酒袋子成为我们下个总统的话
a bloated booze bag to be our next president.
- 奥布莱恩 - 奥布莱恩是个酒鬼?
- O'Brien. - So O'Brien's a lush?
答案和艾莉诺罗斯福舔阴么是一样的?
Did Eleanor Roosevelt eat pussy?
喔! 我的天啊
Oh! Oh, Jesus.
天啊 抱歉 在白宫我们都是这么说话的
Oh, God, I'm sorry. It's the way we talk in the White House.
我都没意识到 我不会再这么说了
I'm not even aware I'm doing it anymore.
哇哦 我是说 你看上去这么...
Wow. I mean, you seem so...
- 然而... - 嘿 也不一定是真的
- and then... whew. - Hey, it may not even be true.
她到底是舔阴或者
Did she eat pussy or did she
宾尼法尼亚大道一路指交下去
just fingerbang her way down Pennsylvania Avenue?
日了我的嘴 我又这么说了
Fuck my mouth. I'm doing it again.
我了个天啊 哇哦
Jiminy Cricket. Wow.
他妈的 显然我们虔诚信来生的代孕妈妈
Damn it. Apparently our born-again surrogate
超级反对病危不抢救 所以总统拔了她妈妈的插头之后
is super against DNR, so when POTUS pulled the plug on MOTUS,
她就改变主意了
she started having second thoughts.
你跟她解释了
Did you explain to her that
神的存在是没有科学依据的吗?
there is no scientific evidence of a higher power?
这酸奶放了多久了?
How long has this yogurt been in here?
千万别拘束 迈克
Make yourself at home, Mike.
别吃香蕉就行 那是蜡制的
Don't eat the bananas. They're wax.
- 收到 - 内华达来了坏消息
- Copy that. - Shit news from Nevada.
- 什么? - 新的票数倾向奥布莱恩
- What? - The new votes are tilting heavily toward O'Brien.
显然他们大都是缺席的军人选举人票
Apparently most of them are military absentees.
当然了 达顿堡 这就都说得通了
Of course. Fort Dutton. It all makes sense.
不不不不 一点都说不通
No, no, no. That doesn't make any sense.
内达华是支持我的 我才应该是总统
Nevada is my state. I'm gonna be president.
我要成为史上选举出的第一位总统女士
I'm gonna be the first elected lady president.
我会有个特别棒的就职典礼 到时候会有比利·乔给我唱歌
I'm gonna have a lovely inauguration. Billy Joel is gonna sing.
所以你们必须马上停止票数重计
So you guys have to stop the recount.
- 等一下 你说什么? - 停止计票
- I'm sorry, what? - Stop the count.
- 盖瑞 闭嘴 女士 这不行 - 我不管
- Shut up, Gary. Ma'am, we can't. - I don't care.
火车已经大庭广众之下驶离站点
The train has very publically
而且高速运行了
left the station and derailed at high speed.
- 你必须停止计票 - 女士
- You got to stop the count. - Ma'am,
这简直是个180度大转弯啊
this would look like a size-14 flip-flop.
- 我们真的不能... - 我他妈不管!
- We really can't... - I don't give a fuck!
你要像安妮·弗兰克的犹太成人礼一样取消票数重计
You're gonna cancel this recount like Anne Frank's bat mitzvah.
好的 马上就办 虽然我觉得已经来不及了
Yeah, I'm on it, though I think the DJ already spent the deposit.
现在就办... 喂 艾米 是的
I'm on it right... yeah, Amy. Yeah.
我已经受够失败了!
I'm tired of losing things!
我们提出申请 希望后来找到的票数
We would like to file a motion to exclude
可以全部作废
all pending ballots from the recount.
柯林斯小姐 你知道你现在说的话
Ms. Collins, you do realize that what you're saying
和昨天完全相反么?
is in diametric opposition to the case you presented yesterday?
既然最后期限已过
If the deadline has passed,
为何要允许继续计票呢?
why is the recount allowed to continue?
反对 法官大人 必须继续计票
Objection, Your Honor. The count must continue.
我们告诉"傻蛋 蠢蛋 奸蛋"
Did we tell "Huey, Dewey, and Rapey"
现在的口号是"停止计票"而不是"票数重计"了么?
that it's "Stop the Count" Now and not "Count Every Vote"?
该死的
Shit.
票数重计 票数重计
Count every vote. Count every vote.
他不是奥布莱恩那边的么?
Doesn't he work for O'Brien?
当然不是了 天呐 快点喊吧 理查德
No. Jesus. Come on, Richard, no.
- 票数重计! - 乔纳!
- Count every vote! - Jonah!
- 票数重计! - 理查德!
- Count every vote! - Richard!
快别喊了 你俩傻缺!
Stop protesting, you idiots!
票数重计! 票数重计!
Count every vote! Count every vote!
让我被暗杀吧
Maybe I'll get assassinated.
三一圣公教堂
马里兰 肯伍德
赛琳娜 赛琳娜 赛琳娜
Selina, Selina, Selina.
- 干嘛? - 人生充满起伏
- What? - Life takes so many turns.
- 是的 - 我希望你明白我的心意
- Yeah. - I just want you to know where I'm coming from.
- 好吧 - 莫妮卡是可爱的
- All right. - Monica, she's sweet,
她很贴心 但她只是暂时的
she's lovely, she's short-term.
她只是目前伴我度过漫漫长夜的人
She's something to get me through the long nights for now.
安德鲁 你知道现在是葬礼 对吧?
Andrew, you know that we're at a funeral, right?
- 我们不是在地中海俱乐部度假 - 在我心里...
- We're not at Club Med. - In here...
从来都是你
it's always been you.
在教堂里
In a church.
- 总统女士 - 汤姆
- Madam President. - Oh, Tom.
- 深表遗憾 请节哀 - 谢谢你
- I'm so sorry for your loss. - Thank you very much.
感谢你能前来 汤姆 我十分感激
Thanks for being here, Tom. I appreciate it.
我看到查理·贝尔德在这
I see that Charlie Baird is here.
是啊 他一大早飞过来的
Yes. Yeah, he flew in this morning.
那么此时此刻的美国经济靠谁挽救呢?
So who's fisting the American economy while he's here?
你是认真的吗 汤姆?
Really, Tom?
抱歉 总统女士
My apologies, Madam President.
- 天啊 - 查理
- God. - Charlie.
- 汤米 - 嗯?
- Tommy. - Yeah?
- 夫人 - 请稍等一下
- Ma'am. - Oh, hang on two seconds.
- 好啊 - 好
- Hi. - Hi.
- 你好 盖瑞 - 好
- Hi, Gary. - Hi.
你前夫 葬礼上也等不及要谈生意啊
Wow, your ex, not afraid to mix business with mourning.
对啊 他见到你多久之后就
Oh, yeah. How soon after meeting you
开始推销他近期的投资计划了?
did he ask you to invest in his latest venture?
- 足足有17秒 我掐了表的 - 真的吗?
- 17 seconds. I timed it. - Really?
一些只赚不亏的
Some can't-lose scheme
巴西第三大连锁酒店的投资计划
about the third largest hotel chain in Brazil.
- "只赚不亏" - 只赚不亏啊
- "Can't lose." - Can't lose.
我得去看看我钱包还在不在了
Got to see if I still have my wallet.
- 夫人 恕我打扰一下 - 好的?
- Ma'am, sorry to interrupt. - Yeah?
- 悼词都准备好了 - 好的
- The eulogy is all set. - Okay.
- 附上那个关于弹钢琴的小故事 - 可谓完美
- And I added the good piano anecdote. - Perfect.
- 这应该不太好吧... - 没事儿 能成
- I don't know if that was the best... - No, it works.
安德鲁
Andrew.
请问我能参加那个巴西投资不?
Can anybody get in on this Brazil thing?
我还得花钱买个娃
I got a baby to pay for.
拜托让我放那首蒂姆·麦格罗的曲子
Please let me play the Tim McGraw song.
行吗? 都准备好了
Okay? I have it all cued up.
讲真 凯瑟琳
Seriously, Catherine,
这是场悼念会 不是纳斯卡车赛[一场收视率奇高的美国汽车赛事]
this is a funeral, not a NASCAR race.
我没时间给你倒腾这个
I don't have the time for this right now.
那您什么时候才有时间 妈? 什么时候?
When do you have the time, then, Mom? When?
- 小点声 - 好吧 因为你不喜欢蒂姆·麦格罗
- Shh. - Okay? Because you don't like Tim McGraw,
所以人人就不该喜欢蒂姆·麦格罗了
then nobody is supposed to like Tim McGraw.
凯瑟琳 你再也不准
Catherine, you are forbidden
提"蒂姆·麦格罗"了
from saying the words "Tim McGraw" Ever again.
太不可理喻了 外婆说你说得太对了
Unbelievable. Mee-Maw was so right about you.
- 你说这话什么意思? - 打扰了 女士
- What is that supposed to mean? - Pardon me, ma'am.
- 打扰一下 能耽误你几分钟时间吗? - 什么?
- Pardon me. Could I borrow you for a minute? - What?
我刚刚跟卡塔尔的大使
I've just been kibitzing with the Qatari ambassador,
默罕默德·本·纳萨尔·本·哈里发·阿里·贾法尔聊了一下
Mohammed bin Nasser bin Khalifa Al Jaffar.
千万别让他签宾客册
Please don't have him sign the guest book.
好的 他带来了一条中国方面的消息
Yeah, he comes bringing a message from China.
为什么中国会在卡塔尔掺一脚?
Why would China go through Qatar?
卡塔尔乐意给他们掺和
Qataris love to insert themselves.
- 他们想进行肮脏的PY交易 - 肛交了?
- They're wet-fingered. - They're into ass play?
不 他们对感知官场的盛行风气很有一套
No, they have a gift for sensing prevailing political winds.
他们肯定也喜欢肛交
I'll bet they're into ass play, too.
你带进来的那些人
Those people that you bring in,
最后会带来新的人 如此以往 你就会从中得到分红
as they bring in people, you get a piece of that.
我会得到分红
I get a piece of that.
源源不绝
In perpetuity.
- 总统女士 - 大使先生
- Madam President. - Mr. Ambassador.
我知道你有则消息要捎给我
So I understand you have a message for me.
- 我要说的内容是严格保密的 - 嗯哼
- What I say to you is in the strictest of confidence. - Mm-hmm.
您扬言对我们的中国朋友进行制裁
The sanctions you have threatened against our friends in China
这会给中国泡沫经济造成巨大的负面影响
may undermine their very fragile economy
特别是在经济如此不景气的当下
at a most inopportune moment.
但是 用减轻经济压力做交换
But in exchange for easing the economic pressure,
他们愿意开展一次间接谈话
they would be open to indirect talks.
都谈些什么呢?
What is on the table?
噢 几乎所有
Oh, everything.
从气候变化到人权主义
From climate change to human rights.
请您与我保持联系
We shall be in touch.
谢谢您 大使阿里...
Thank you, Ambassador Al...
好的
Okay.
神秘啊?
Well, that was mysterious, right?
- 女士 他们都在等着你呢 - 嗯?
- Ma'am. They're ready for you. - Yeah?
开场吧
Let's get this show on the road.
今天 我们聚集在这里
We are gathered together today
是为了铭记凯瑟琳·卡尔弗特·伊顿的一生
to remember the life of Catherine Calvert Eaton.
这个中国的事应该是个名流千古的机会是吧?
This China thing is like legacy material, right?
或者是让我得诺贝尔和平奖的那种
Nobel Peace Prize material.
什么?
What?
我等下再告诉你
I'll tell you after.
现在就告诉我
Tell me now.
凯伦阻止不了计票
Karen couldn't stop the count.
我们正式输了内华达
We officially lost Nevada,
所以我们必须在国会上赢回来
so we're gonna have to fight it out in Congress.
- 还有... - 还有什么?
- And... - And what?
还有啥?
What else?
鉴于新的投票数都流向了奥布莱恩 我们...
With all the new votes going to O'Brien, we've...
肯特你来说
Kent.
我们也失去了大众选票
We lost the popular vote.
哦天啊
Oh, God.
我很抱歉 女士
I'm so sorry, ma'am.
节哀
Sorry for your loss.
好吧
Yeah.
行吧
Okay.
汝其勿悲
I grieve with thee.
谢谢你 肯特
Oh, thank you, Kent.
仪式正式开始 下面有请其女
As we begin our service, we will now hear from her daughter,
赛琳娜·梅耶总统上台讲话
President Selina Meyer.
我的母亲有一架好钢琴
My mother had a good piano.
对不起
I'm sorry.
有太多的情感向我涌来
It's just all sort of hitting me right now.
我失去...
I have lost...
太多了
so much.
对不起 我做不到 我做不到
I'm sorry. I can't. I can't.
凯瑟琳 放那首蒂姆·麦格罗的什么鬼吧
Catherine, play the Tim McGraw thing.
# 她那挂在门后的宽檐帽 #
# Her hat is hanging by the door #
# 是在那年购于墨西哥 #
# The one she bought in mexico #
# 它为她遮风挡雨 #
# It blocked the wind, it stopped the rain #
这不公平 这就是不公平
Just not fair. This is just not fair.
# 她那平安夜买的鞋子 #
# The shoes she bought on christmas eve #
# 她总是在说它们在呼唤她的名字 #
# She laughed and said they called her name #
# 好像它们在门厅等候多时 #
# It's like they're waiting in the hall #
# 等待着她穿戴整齐 #
# For her to slip them on #
- 非常感人的悼词 - 谢谢你 乔治
- A very moving eulogy. - Oh, thank you, George.
你感觉好点儿的时候 你 我还有凯瑟琳需要
When you feel up to it, you and Catherine and I should sit down
讨论一下房产的事情 看看你能拿到什么
and discuss the estate and how you fit into all of it.
我能拿到什么?
How I fit into the estate?
遗产隔代继承并不少见
It's not uncommon for an inheritance to skip a generation
你母亲决定
and your mother decided
把她大部分房产传给凯瑟琳
to leave the bulk of her estate to Catherine.
大部分?
The bulk?
- 一切都会好起来的 - 对
- It'll all be fine. - Yes.
- 精彩的演讲 - 谢谢你
- Great speech. - Thank you.
- 喜欢那首歌 - 好吧
- Love that song. - Okay.
我之前说过的话就算了
Sorry about what I said earlier.
我是悲伤过头了
That was the grief talking.
- 好的 - 凯瑟琳 亲爱的...?
- All right. - Catherine, honey...?
我需要张面纸
I need a tissue
- 我没有纸 - 要你何用
- I don’t have a tissue - Well, that’s useless
- 女士? - 怎么?
- Ma’am? - Yes?
我恨死我爸爸了
I hated my father
谢谢你了汤姆
Thank you Tom
- 杀向国会? - 杀向国会
- To congress we go? - To congress we go, yeah
祝贺你
Congratulation